expatexchange.com 2015-12-19

# Expat Exchange Privacy Policy - Expats - Moving Overseas - International Living - International Jobs - Expatriate

At ExpatExchange.com, the privacy of our visitors is of extreme importance to us. This privacy policy document outlines the types of personal information is received and collected by ExpatExchange.com and how it is used. If you require any more information or have any questions about our privacy policy, please feel free to contact us by email at [help@expatexchange.com](mailto:help@expatexchange.com). 

ExpatExchange.com collects your personal information when you register to use our message boards, answer one of our surveys or reports, fill out other forms or request information about our services. Additionally, we use cookies and collect your IP address (for security and management of proper message board decorum). 

ExpatExchange.com uses this information to improve our service, enhance security, ensure we answer your requests to our satisfaction and to conduct accurate research and reporting of an anonymous nature. 

ExpatExchange.com does not distribute your personal information to any third party for any purpose without your permission. This includes selling, renting or sharing of this information. The only exceptions are as follows: 

To investigate fraud or other illicit activities. This includes the investigation of physical threats against any person, the violation of ExpatExchange.com's privacy policy or member agreement, or any other situation in which ExpatExchange.com or Burlingame Interactive is required by law. 

Responses to legal actions, court orders, subpoenas. 

To Defend ExpatExchange.com and Burlingame Interactive against any legal actions or the establishment of our legal rights. 

In the event ExpatExchange.com is acquired by or merged with another legal entity, we will attempt to notify you via e-mail before any information is transferred to that legal entity and is governed by a new privacy policy. 

ExpatExchange.com does not currently offer any services to children under the age of 13, and we have no desire to collect any information from anyone under the age of 18. 

ExpatExchange.com does NOT include selling, renting or sharing your information with third parties. 

## Log Files

Like many other Web sites, ExpatExchange.com makes use of log files. The information inside the log files includes internet protocol ( IP ) addresses, type of browser, Internet Service Provider ( ISP ), date/time stamp, referring/exit pages, and number of clicks to analyze trends, administer the site, track user’s movement around the site, and gather demographic information. IP addresses, and other such information are not linked to any information that is personally identifiable. 

## Cookies and Web Beacons

ExpatExchange.com does use cookies to store information about visitors preferences, record user-specific information on which pages the user access or visit, customize Web page content based on visitors browser type or other information that the visitor sends via their browser. 

## DoubleClick DART Cookie

  * Google, as a third party vendor, uses cookies to serve ads on ExpatExchange.com.
  * Google's use of the DART cookie enables it to serve ads to users based on their visit to ExpatExchange.com and other sites on the Internet. 
  * Users may opt out of the use of the DART cookie by visiting the Google ad and content network privacy policy at the following URL - http://www.google.com/privacy_ads.html 

Some of our advertising partners may use cookies and web beacons on our site. Our advertising partners include .... 

Google Adsense

Commission Junction

Clickbank

Chitika

Linkshare

Amazon

These third-party ad servers or ad networks use technology to the advertisements and links that appear on ExpatExchange.com send directly to your browsers. They automatically receive your IP address when this occurs. Other technologies ( such as cookies, JavaScript, or Web Beacons ) may also be used by the third-party ad networks to measure the effectiveness of their advertisements and / or to personalize the advertising content that you see. 

ExpatExchange.com has no access to or control over these cookies that are used by third-party advertisers. 

You should consult the respective privacy policies of these third-party ad servers for more detailed information on their practices as well as for instructions about how to opt-out of certain practices. ExpatExchange.com's privacy policy does not apply to, and we cannot control the activities of, such other advertisers or web sites. 

If you wish to disable cookies, you may do so through your individual browser options. More detailed information about cookie management with specific web browsers can be found at the browsers' respective websites.
